emedoutlet.com 2009-06-24

# Canadian Pharmacy Online, Cheap Online Mexican Pharmacy

|  |  |   
---  
PRIVACY POLICY  
  It is our top priority to protect your privacy. We do collect personal information about you in order to fill your prescription orders and we pledge to maintain the confidentiality of that information. We do not sell, rent or give away the information you have entrusted to us. This notice describes our current privacy policy and practices.  
**Privacy And Security**  
  We have strict policies and procedures in place to safeguard the privacy and security of your personal information. Your personal information, including the data contained in our computers, is protected from unauthorized access. Its use is restricted to employees and others having a business need for the information.Emedoutlet provides a SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) certificate and 128 Bit Encryption as per industry standards in protection against hackers and web violators, to ensure the protection of your information.  
**Types And Use Of Personal Information Collected**  
  The personal information we collect from you and about you is used to provide you with discount prescription medicines. This information varies depending upon whether you are a client or a prospective client. Examples of personal information we may collect from you or about you include: your name, address, telephone number, medical information and credit card information.  
  The information may be obtained from a telephone conversation, application, prescription form or from other sources, such as medical forms or reports. We maintain personal information regarding your transactions with Emedoutlet and we may request additional information in order to provide you with our products.  
**Safeguarding Your Medical Information**  
  Emedoutlet does not rent, sell, or give away your personally identifiable medical information to anyone for marketing purposes. We will only use and share personally identifiable medical information for specifically requested transactions and for those purposes required or permitted by law.  
**When We May Disclose Information**  
  Emedoutlet respects the confidentiality of your personal information. There are circumstances in which we may disclose to third parties information we have about you in order to conduct our business, including processing a prescription transaction that you request or authorize. We will make these disclosures only when they are permitted or required by law. These disclosures may include providing information in response to a request by regulatory or governmental authorities, other administrators, auditors, or consultants. We may also provide the pharmacy or doctor with access to your personal information that is needed to administer your business and provide service to you. They may also use this information to advise you of additional products and services offered through their company.  
  We do not rent, sell, or disclose any of your personal information, regardless of whether you are a current or former customer. Should your relationship with Emedoutlet end, we will continue to limit disclosures of your personal information in accordance with our stated privacy policy and practices just as we do for those who maintain a continuing relationship with us.  
  We welcome your inquiries. Please email us at [noreply@emedoutlet.com](mailto:noreply@emedoutlet.com)  
|   
|    Anti-Convulsant        
---  
   Acne        
   ADHD        
   Alcohol & Drug Treatment        
   Allergy & Sinus        
   Alzheimers        
   Anthelmintic        
   Anti Coagulant        
   Anti hemorrhoids        
   Anti Viral        
   Anti-Cancer        
   Anti-Depressant        
   Anti-Emetic        
   Anti-Gout        
   Anti-Parkinsonion        
   Anti-Smoking        
   Antibiotics        
   Antifungal        
   Antipsychotic        
   Arthritis        
   Asthma        
   Beauty & Skin Care        
   Birth Control        
   Bladder - Prostate        
   Charity & Aid Org        
   Dental Care        
   Diabetes        
   Epilepsy        
   Eye Care        
   Gastro Health        
   Hair Loss        
   Heart & Blood Pressure        
   Herbal Enhancers        
   Herbal Health        
   HIV & Herpes        
   Homeopathic Medicine        
   Hormones        
   Immunosuppressive        
   Infertility Therapy        
   Mens Health        
   Mens Herbal Health        
   Muscle Relaxant        
   Osteoporosis        
   Pain Relief        
   Pet Care        
   Pure Herbal        
   Sleep Aid        
   Tubercolosis        
   Weight Loss        
   Womens Health        
   Womens Herbal Health
